<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.iroi-mn.org"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
 <title>International Religious Organization of India</title>
 <link>http://www.iroi-mn.org</link>
 <description></description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>Home</title>
 <link>http://www.iroi-mn.org/home</link>
 <description>&lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #8b4500;&quot;&gt;Welcome to our homepage&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: small;&quot;&gt;Jai Shri Krishna to all&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a religious and educational organization, IROI is particularly related to human nature and spirituality and willing to give Vedic, religious, spiritual, and educational knowledge to all Hindus and also non-Hindus living in our societies on international levels. IROI is literary based and believe in the philosophy of some of the very important Hindu scriptures like Shrimad Bhagavad-Gita, Srimad-Bhagavatam and the Vishnu Purana to find the right path for its audiences. Before that, to understand Hinduism and its related topics are extremely important to define, and follow the path of bhakti including: the meaning of bhakti, l types of bhakti, l how to cultivate bhakti, l self-forgetfulness in bhakti, l nine forms of bhakti, and l fruits of bhakti. Bhakti can benefit all human beings equally, living anywhere and in all societies as well as giving the right direction to a longer, higher spiritual life, only through the process of bhakti yoga.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditionally there are nine forms of bhakti yoga. Bhakti Yoga is generally considered the easiest of the four general paths to liberation or moksha (the others being Karma, Raja, and Janana Yoga), and especially so within the current age of Kali Yuga (according to the Hindu cycle of time). In scriptures such as the Bhagavata Purana, bhakti is described as a perfect stage in itself which surpasses even moksha as a level of spiritual realization. Hindu movements in which Bhakti Yoga is the main practice are called bhakti movements. IROI is a Vaishnava Bhakti Movement to spread the bhakti of Lord Krishna describing him as Lila Avatar (Lila Avatar means divine play of Lord Krishna) and his various Lilas (divine play) to all audiences in our society on all levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.iroi-mn.org/home&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;read more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 04:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>seadmin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">2 at http://www.iroi-mn.org</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
